Guide to the Friendship House Association records, 1904-1992 MS2142
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Financial Records, 1914-1990; MS2142 Series 4; 5.5 Linear feet (Box 82, Box 81, Box 72, Box 76, Box 75, Box 74, Box 73, Box 80, Box 79, Box 78, Box 77)
  - Statements of Revenue and Expenses to 03/1980 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Statements of Revenue and Expenses to 05/1980 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Statements of Revenue and Expenses to 11/1980 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Statements of Revenue and Expenses to 12/1980 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Statement, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Finances, figures FY, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Sources of funding FY, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Trust account, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Bequest - Ruth Hendershot Trust, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Bequest - Emily Lyman Storer, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Grant request, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Grant request replies, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Expenditures - Revenue, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Investments, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Revised operating budget, 1980-1981 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Financial statements 06/1981 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Revenue and expenditures FY, 1989-1981 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Expenditures and revenue to 06/1981 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Grant and request, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Foundation Grant, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Development campaign, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Development campaign - contracts, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Development campaign - small contributions, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - United Way requests FY, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Fund raising, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Tax matters, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - UPO budget cuts impact on Friendship House finances, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Expenditures and revenue FY 1980, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 35)
    - done in 1981
  - Estimated costs 06/1981 (Box 82, Folder 36)
  - Grant application for service exchange program, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 37)
  - Foundation Grant, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 38)
  - Revised operating budget 07/1981-06/1982 (Box 82, Folder 39)
  - Revenue and expenditures FY, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 40)
  - Revenue and expenditures FY, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 41)
  - Funding sources FY, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 42)
  - Financial figures 07/1981-06/1982 - FY (Box 82, Folder 43)
  - Budget FY 1982, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 44)
  - Office on Aging - monthly report 05/1982 (Box 82, Folder 45)
  - Finances and budget FY, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 46)
  - Statement - revenue and expenses FY, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 47)
  - Statement from Annual Report, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 48)
  - Donor list from Annual Report, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 49)
- Funding Sources, 1940-1981; MS2142 Series 5; 14.5 Linear feet (Box 93, Box 94, Box 91, Box 92, Box 89, Box 90, Box 87, Box 88, Box 107, Box 111, Box 109, Box 108, Box 95, Box 110, Box 102, Box 103, Box 100, Box 101, Box 106, Box 104, Box 105, Box 84, Box 83, Box 86, Box 85, Box 98, Box 99, Box 96, Box 97)
  This series contains newspapers, reports, budgets, and grant proposals which document supplemental funding for the Friendship House Association. The materials cover the dates 1940-81. The bulk of the collection materials is dated from 1965-79.
  The longest continuous funding to Friendship House was from the United Way. It was the only large agency funding in the early years. It was a funder of Friendship House from its earliest years of its existence. The previous names for the United Way agency were The Community Chest (sometimes called Red Feather Campaign), United Community Services, United Givers Fund, and finally United Way. In addition to these materials are records relating to support provided by the United Planning Organization. United Planning Organization: Neighborhood Development Program 1964-81, Neighborhood Advisory Committee 1965-81, Neighborhood Legal Service 1965-69, Consumer Action Program 1965-78, Neighborhood Development Youth Program 1966-68, Community Organization Unit 1970-82, VISTA 1965-67, Community Action Program 1966-76, Head Start 1966-69.
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 83)
  - New UPO grant to Friendship House - first grant 01/1965 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - UPO - General correspondence, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Community Relations file, 1964-1965 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Research Division monthly report 10/1965 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Research Division monthly report 11/1965 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - UPO Newsletters "Facts" January and 04/1965 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - UPO Newsletter "Emphasis" 06/1965 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - UPO contract (FY 1967) (Box 83, Folder 10)
    1965
  - UPO Audit 12/1965 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Training Proposal, 1965-1966 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Charter of organization - Friendship House and UPO, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - UPO Directory, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - UPO "Centers and Services" report on services, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - UPO Request, explanation, agreement, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Research Division monthly report 01/1966 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Research Division monthly report 02/1966 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Meetings, notices, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Friendship House Report on its Neighborhood Development Program operated under UPO contract of, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Manpower Program, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - UPO Newsletter, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Proposal and aid projects to UPO funding, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Amendment on extensions, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Request for final report, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Budget Request 1967, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 84)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): 1967 Budget Request, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): UPO agreement, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Directory, programs, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursement 03/1966 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursement 04/1966 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursement 05/1966 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursement 06/1966 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursement 09/1966 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursement 10/1966 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursement 11/1966 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursement 12/1966 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Research Division Monthly Report 03/1966 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Research Division Monthly Report 04/1966 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Research Division Monthly Report 05/1966 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Research Division Monthly Report 06/1966 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Research Division Monthly Report 07/1966 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Research Division Monthly Report 08/1966 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Research Division Monthly Report (and Community Field Survey), 11/1966 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - UPO Newsletters March-04/1966 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - UPO Newsletters May-06/1966 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - UPO Newsletters July-08/1966 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - UPO Newsletters September-10/1966 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - UPO Newsletters November-12/1966 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Statement of Mr. James Banks, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Volunteer hours discussion, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 85)
  - Report on the Uses of UPO services - Research Division Report January-04/1967 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - UPO Newsletters "On The Go", 1966 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    1967
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Organization chart, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - UPO 1967 budget request, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Agreement - Amendment, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - UPO "A Brief Outline of its Program and Structure", 1967 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Statement of the President, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursement, 01/1967 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursemen. 02/1967 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursemen, 03/1967 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursemen. 04/1967 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursemen, 07/1967 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Extension Agreement 07/1967 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - UPO Newsletters, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Article "City of Broken Dreams, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Organization chart, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Agreement, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Bylaws of UPO, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Program, statements, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Board of Trustees, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Request for Reimbursement 02/1968 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Program for the Aged - Project FIND, 1967-1968 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Location of programs, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Poor People's Campaign Participation, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - "UPO ON The Go" article on Friendship House, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 86)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Extension agreement, 1969 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Daily log of field workers' contacts (samples), 1969 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Brochure "UPO: Its Mission", 1970 ca. (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - UPO brochure, undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - UPO Directory, 1970 ca. (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - UPO Library book list, 1970 ca. (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Newsletter 01/1970 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Newsletter 02/1970 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - UPO Directory, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's Request for Reimbursement October-12/1971 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - UPO Newsletters, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Evaluation, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - UPO Newsletters, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Grant Request, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): End of funding (section 221) Instructions, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Amendment to UPO Agreement, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Notebook - Organizational History of UPO, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Correspondence re audit, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contractor's reports, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): PACTS program, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - UPO's proposal to OEO for Meals Delivery System, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - UPO Newsletter, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 87)
  - "UPO-Its Mission" - brochure, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Re budget, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Re budget, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Re budget, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Financial statements, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Program Project Review Report, 10/1975-09/1976 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Report of Contractors, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Request for Reimbursement January-06/1975 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Request for Reimbursement. August-10/1975 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Request for Reimbursement, September-12/1975 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Request for Reimbursement. 09/1975 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Request for Reimbursement, 10/1975 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Alcoholism Project, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - UPO Newspaper "Community" 07/1975 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - "UPO `76.Making it Happen", 1976 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Annual Report, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Budget figures, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Transportation Demonstration Grant Proposal, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Scope of Services, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Consumer Price Index Summary, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Statistical Report, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 88)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Report on Twelve Community Action Programs, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - UPO Newsletter "Community" 03/1976 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - UPO Newsletter article on Friendship House, 06/1976 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - UPO Newsletter, August-10/1976 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Directory of Head Start Programs' Staff, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Budget figures 10/1976-09/1977 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Program Progress Review Report 10/76-9/77, 1976-1977 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Program Progress Review Report, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Program Progress Review Report, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - UPO Monthly Report 06/1977 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report October-12/1977 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Publication "UPO 77-Progress and Hope", 1977 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Agreement, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Alcoholism Project, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Problems Identified, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Housing Development Proposal, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - UPO Newspaper - "Community" January-08/1977 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 89)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Agreement with Friendship House, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Subject Agreement, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Manual, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - UPO Director's Meeting 06/1978 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 01/1978 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 02/1978 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 03/1978 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 04/1978 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 05/1978 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 06/1978 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 07/1978 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 08/1978 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 09/1978 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 10/1978 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 11/1978 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 12/1978 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Voucher for Non-Federal Share - form, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Program Progress Review Form, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Project Progress Review Report - second quarter, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Program Progress Review (re Clothing Center), 1978 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Agency Activities form, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Consumer Affairs Group - Annual Review Report, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Alcoholism Project, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Requests for Special Funds, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - UPO Newsletter, 06/1978 (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 90)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Memo of understanding, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Application, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Work program and budget summary, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 01/1979 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 05/1979 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 06/1979 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 07/1979 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Contractor's Report 09/1979 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Reimbursement Reports January-05/1979 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Reimbursement Reports September-12/1979 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Foster Grandparents Program, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - UPO Newsletter, 03/1979 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Voucher for Non-Federal Share (Project LINK-program for the aged) 08/1979 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Request for Special Funds, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Annual Summary, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Youth Services Section - annual summary, 1979-1980 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Contract, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Project Progress Review Report, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Budget figures, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Request for Reimbursement January-06/1980 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Request for Reimbursement September-12/1980 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Appeals procedure for those denied service, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Correspondence and budget agreements, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Monthly Request for Reimbursement, January-04/1981 (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Re grant of, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 25)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Newsletter "Community", 1981 (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Budget information, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - United Planning Organization (UPO): Reimbursement, 01/1982 (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 91)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: NDP explained, 1964 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Budget Request 1965, 1964 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Program described, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Finances, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Meeting notes, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Advisory Committee, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Training course, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consultant's committee, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consultant's committee, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Headstart, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Discussions with neighborhood leaders, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Community organization programs - Block Clubs, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Progress Reports, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Metropolitan Citizens Advisory Council, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Anti-Poverty programs, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Request for refunding and expansion, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Budget Request FY 1966, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Budget Request FY 1966, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Neighborhood Development Program final report, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 92)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Agreement with Friendship House 01/1965 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Audit of NDP, 01/1965-12/1966 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Correspondence, 01/1965-06/1965 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consultant's Committee 02/1965 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consultant's Committee 03/1965 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    Folder 6 does not exist
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consultant's Committee 04/1965 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Graduation of neighborhood workers 04/1965 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consultant's Committee 05/1965 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consultant's Committee 06/1965 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consultant's Committee 07/1965 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Correspondence, 07/1965-12/1965 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consultant's Committee, 07/1965-08/1965 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Meeting, 08/1965 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: NDP - Tour of the neighborhood, 09/1965 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consultant's Committee 09/1965 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consultant's Committee 10/1965 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consultant's Committee 11/1965 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Citizens' Advisory Committee 12/1965 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consultant's Committee 12/1965 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Budget material, undated (Box 92, Folder 21)